{
    "subject": "resource/The_Blue_Lamp",
    "predicate": "property/screenplay",
    "object": "resource/T.E.B._Clarke",
    "human_readable": "The screenplay of The Blue Lamp was written by T.E.B. Clarke.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9851720333099365,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for The Blue Lamp besides T.E.B. Clarke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9600270390510559,
            "question": "What film's screenplay was written by T.E.B. Clarke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9550447463989258,
            "question": "What is the title of the screenplay written by T.E.B. Clarke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9518968462944031,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for The Blue Lamp?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9298406839370728,
            "question": "Is T.E.B. Clarke known for writing screenplays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8916078805923462,
            "question": "What is the name of the person who wrote the screenplay for The Blue Lamp?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8265522718429565,
            "question": "Is T.E.B. Clarke a famous screenwriter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.826188862323761,
            "question": "Can you name a film with a screenplay by T.E.B. Clarke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6733216047286987,
            "question": "What other works has T.E.B. Clarke written?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5015543699264526,
            "question": "What genre is The Blue Lamp?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The screenplay of The Blue Lamp was written by T.E.B. Clarke.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2673_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other works has T.E.B. Clarke written?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2673_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film with a screenplay by T.E.B. Clarke?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2673_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is T.E.B. Clarke a famous screenwriter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2673_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2673_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about The Blue Lamp, including its director (Basil Dearden), cast members (Jack Warner, Jimmy Hanley, Dirk Bogarde, etc.), and writer (T.E.B. Clarke). This supports the triple that the screenplay of The Blue Lamp was written by T.E.B. Clarke."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that T.E.B. Clarke wrote the screenplay for \"The Blue Lamp,\" which supports the statement that the screenplay of \"The Blue Lamp\" was written by T.E.B. Clarke."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}